Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series XX: Artifacts, Artwork and Memorabilia
  - Subseries 7: Equipment and Printing Artifacts
    - McCormick-Armstrong Company, "A Chart of the History of Printing in America," chart, 1932 (Box 1263, Folder 1)
    - Paper samples (Box 1263, Folder 2-10)
    - Paper and printing samples (Box 1263, Folder 11)
    - Proof sheets, European, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1263, Folder 12-13)
    - Magazine covers and tear sheets, 1933-1934 (Box 1264, Folder 1)
    - Paper sample (Box 1264, Folder 2)
    - Surgery and Gynecology, three-color separation proofs and plates, 1965 (Box 1264, Folder 3)
    - Proof sheets, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 1264, Folder 4)
    - Proof sheets, European, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 1264, Folder 5-11)
    - To Be A Good Printer, negatives (Box 1265, Folder 1-2)
    - Declaration of Independence facsimile, positives, negatives and proofs, 1979 (Box 1265, Folder 3-4)
    - R. Hoe & Company, sign (Box 1265, Folder 5)
    - Miehle, sign (Box 1266)
    - Suggestion box, circa 1960s (Box 1266)
    - Four electro printing plates (Box 1267)
    - Three electro printing plates (Box 1268)
    - Photocopy of bibliographic cards for electro printing plates (Box 1268)
    - Product sample, Covey Leadership Center, First Things First, audio cassette kit, 1994 (Box 1269)
    - Product sample, Eyewitness, Encyclopedia of Science, multimedia kit, 1994 (Box 1269)
    - First color separation made at RR Donnelley (Box 1270, Folder 1)
    - James Gilbert Wagner, "D'Artagnan," portfolio (Box 1270, Folder 2)
    - Chicago Athletic Association, "Collector's Portfolio of Gold-Etch Prints by Lionel Barrymore," portfolio (Box 1270, Folder 3)
    - Book illustrations, proofs (Box 1270, Folder 4)
    - Last sheet printed at Plymouth Court plant, 1929 (Box 1270, Folder 5)
    - Lakeside Classics, Crest of the Continent illustrations, proofs, 1958 (Box 1270, Folder 6)
    - John F. Cuneo and Company, announcement (Box 1270, Folder 7)
    - Noticias de la Provincia de Californias, facsimile, proofs (Box 1270, Folder 8)
    - "A Celebration of Print," posters, circa 1987 (Box 1271)
    - RR Donnelley, Apollo 11 moon landing, poster, 1969 (Box 1272)
    - Laura Ashley catalog, proof sheets, 1983 (Box 1273)
    - Standard Oil Company, Span, proof sheets, 1962 (Box 1274)
    - Aramco World Magazine, proof sheets, 1983 (Box 1275)
    - Aramco World Magazine, proof sheets, 1983 (Box 1276)
    - Chicago Bulls poster, proof sheet, 1991 (Box 1277)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1278)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1279)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1280)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1281)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1282)
    - Proof sheets (Box 1283)
    - People magazine, Nyloprint plate (Box 1284)
    - Gravure cylinder plates (Box 1284)
    - Microscope (Box 1285)
    - Cylinder strength testing instrument (Box 1286)
    - Set type (Box 1287)
    - Typesetting tray (Box 1287)
    - Cast iron scale (Box ITEM 3)
    - Gravure cylinder (Box ITEM 4)
    - Thompson's, restaurant advertisements, circa 1935, Camel cigarette packaging, proof sheets, undated (Box CABINET 1 DRAWER 6, Folder 1)